A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1971-1980 FA401
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1976
  - United States, 1976; 1976/200
    - Ab-Af, 1976 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - Albion College, 1976 (Reel 13, Frame 189)
    - Alfred University, 1976 (Reel 13, Frame 199)
    - Alice Lloyd College (Appalachian Oral History), 1976 (Reel 13, Frame 217)
    - Ag-Al, 1976 (Reel 13, Frame 433)
    - American (A-D), 1976 (Reel 13, Frame 856)
    - American (F-H), 1976 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - American (I-N), 1976 (Reel 14, Frame 247)
    - American (P-U), 1976 (Reel 14, Frame 376)
    - An-Ar, 1976 (Reel 14, Frame 682)
    - Asia Society (Peters, Muriel), 1976 (Reel 14, Frame 1021)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies (C-S), 1976 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Association (A-V), 1976 (Reel 15, Frame 197)
    - As-Az, 1976 (Reel 15, Frame 411)
    - Basura, Nick, 1976 (Reel 15, Frame 621)
    - Battelle Human Affairs Research Centers (Contraceptive Technology), 1976 (Reel 15, Frame 696)
    - Ba, 1976 (Reel 15, Frame 837)
    - Be, 1976 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Bi-Bl, 1976 (Reel 16, Frame 192)
    - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, Inc. (S-W), 1976 (Reel 16, Frame 342)
    - Bo, 1976 (Reel 16, Frame 535)
    - Br, 1976 (Reel 16, Frame 718)
    - Bu, 1976 (Reel 16, Frame 940)
    - California Institute of Technology (H-S), 1976 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - Ca, 1976 (Reel 17, Frame 267)
    - Center for Media Study, 1976 (Reel 17, Frame 454)
    - Center for Media Study (Supplementary Material), 1976 (Reel 17, Frame 630)
    - Center (A-S), 1976 (Reel 17, Frame 862)
    - Ce, 1976 (Reel 17, Frame 1040)
    - Change (Career Guide), 1976 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - Ch, 1976 (Reel 18, Frame 206)
    - Citizen Involvement Network, 1976 (Reel 18, Frame 394)
    - Ci, 1976 (Reel 18, Frame 641)
    - Cl, 1976 (Reel 18, Frame 770)
    - Columbia University (E-W), 1976 (Reel 18, Frame 882)
    - Cod-Col, 1976 (Reel 18, Frame 1064)
    - Community Mental Health Epidemiology Project, 1976 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - Com, 1976 (Reel 19, Frame 173)
    - Cornell University (Acid Rain), 1976 (Reel 19, Frame 424)
    - Cornell University, Acid Rain (Supplementary Material), 1976 (Reel 19, Frame 465)
    - Cornell University (B-V), 1976 (Reel 19, Frame 885)
    - Con-Cor, 1976 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - Council (A-W), 1976 (Reel 20, Frame 278)
    - Cou, 1976 (Reel 20, Frame 598)
    - Cr-Cu, 1976 (Reel 20, Frame 656)
    - Davis, Allen F., 1976 (Reel 20, Frame 708)
    - Da, 1976 (Reel 20, Frame 837)
    - De, 1976 (Reel 20, Frame 972)
    - Di-Dr, 1976 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - Duke University (African Religions Institute), 1976 (Reel 21, Frame 267)
    - Duke University (C-J), 1976 (Reel 21, Frame 444)
    - Du-Dy, 1976 (Reel 21, Frame 488)
    - Ea-Ec, 1976 (Reel 21, Frame 588)
    - Education Development Center (Myers, Charles N.), 1976 (Reel 21, Frame 637)
    - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (I-W), 1976 (Reel 21, Frame 897)
    - Eleutherian Mills Historical Library, 1976 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - Environmental Agenda Task Force, 1976 (Reel 22, Frame 155)
    - Environmental Agenda Task Force (Supplementary Material), 1976 (Reel 22, Frame 411)
    - Ed-Ex, 1976 (Reel 22, Frame 623)
    - Fa-Fe, 1976 (Reel 22, Frame 792)
    - Fi-Fl, 1976 (Reel 22, Frame 896)
    - Ford Foundation (A-T), 1976 (Reel 22, Frame 1001)
    - Furman University (J-P), 1976 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - Fo-Fu, 1976 (Reel 23, Frame 62)
    - Georgetown University (H-S), 1976 (Reel 23, Frame 214)
    - Georgia Institute of Technology (E-I), 1976 (Reel 23, Frame 242)
    - Ga-Ge, 1976 (Reel 23, Frame 307)
    - Gi-Gl, 1976 (Reel 23, Frame 496)
    - Go, 1976 (Reel 23, Frame 733)
    - Graduate Theological Union, 1976 (Reel 23, Frame 847)
    - Grant, Denise L., 1976 (Reel 23, Frame 924)
    - Gr-Gw, 1976 (Reel 23, Frame 941)
    - Harvard University (A-S), 1976 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - Ha, 1976 (Reel 24, Frame 276)
    - He-Hi, 1976 (Reel 24, Frame 570)
    - Ho, 1976 (Reel 24, Frame 704)
    - Hu-Hy, 1976 (Reel 24, Frame 805)
    - Indiana University (Poynter Center), 1976 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
    - Indiana University (Siffin, William J.), 1976 (Reel 25, Frame 239)
    - Institute for the Study of Humanistic Medicine, 1976 (Reel 25, Frame 299)
    - Institute for the Study of Humanistic Medicine (Supplementary Material), 1976 (Reel 25, Frame 406)
    - Institute (A-S), 1976 (Reel 25, Frame 527)
    - International (B-T), 1976 (Reel 25, Frame 803)
    - Iowa State University (H-W), 1976 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
    - I, 1976 (Reel 26, Frame 65)
    - James Association, 1976 (Reel 26, Frame 207)
    - James Association (Supplementary Material), 1976 (Reel 26, Frame 209)
    - Ja-Ji, 1976 (Reel 26, Frame 272)
    - Johns Hopkins University (B-W), 1976 (Reel 26, Frame 372)
    - Jo-Ju, 1976 (Reel 26, Frame 385)
    - Kansas State University (B-F), 1976 (Reel 26, Frame 545)
    - K-Ke, 1976 (Reel 26, Frame 609)
    - Ki-Kn, 1976 (Reel 26, Frame 886)
    - Ko-Ku, 1976 (Reel 26, Frame 915)
    - La, 1976 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
    - Le, 1976 (Reel 27, Frame 100)
    - Library of Congress (Preservation Program), 1976 (Reel 27, Frame 322)
    - Li, 1976 (Reel 27, Frame 377)
    - Long Island University, 1976 (Reel 27, Frame 484)
    - Lo-Ly, 1976 (Reel 27, Frame 501)
    - MacDonald, Jack D., 1976 (Reel 27, Frame 736)
    - Macy Foundation (C-F), 1976 (Reel 27, Frame 757)
    - Management of Wastewater Residuals (Conference), 1976 (Reel 27, Frame 923)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Leadership Campaign), 1976 (Reel 27, Frame 993)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Leadership Campaign (Supplementary Material), 1976 (Reel 27, Frame 997)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (C-W), 1976 (Reel 28, Frame 1)
    - M-Ma, 1976 (Reel 28, Frame 50)
    - Mc, 1976 (Reel 28, Frame 412)
    - Me, 1976 (Reel 28, Frame 500)
    - Michigan State University (E-W), 1976 (Reel 28, Frame 772)
    - Mi, 1976 (Reel 28, Frame 943)
    - Morgan State University (Center for Critical Languages and Cultures), 1976 (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - Moton Memorial Foundation, 1976 (Reel 29, Frame 107)
    - Mo-My, 1976 (Reel 29, Frame 219)
    - National Academy of Sciences (B-W), 1976 (Reel 29, Frame 315)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (H-S), 1976 (Reel 29, Frame 513)
    - National (A), 1976 (Reel 29, Frame 665)
    - National (B), 1976 (Reel 30, Frame 1)
    - National (C-D), 1976 (Reel 30, Frame 287)
    - National Education Association (Roots of America), 1976 (Reel 30, Frame 472)
    - National Education Association, Roots of America (Supplementary Material), 1976 (Reel 30, Frame 476)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (J-L), 1976 (Reel 30, Frame 579)
    - National Farmers Union, 1976 (Reel 30, Frame 805)
    - National (E-I), 1976 (Reel 30, Frame 879)
    - National Research Council (B-C), 1976 (Reel 30, Frame 1054)
    - National (M-U), 1976 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
    - National Women's Education Fund, 1976 (Reel 31, Frame 212)
    - Na, 1976 (Reel 31, Frame 377)
    - Nebolsine, Arcadi, 1976 (Reel 31, Frame 460)
    - New (B-D), 1976 (Reel 31, Frame 636)
    - New (E-S), 1976 (Reel 31, Frame 982)
    - New York City (B-C), 1976 (Reel 32, Frame 1)
    - New York University (C-S), 1976 (Reel 32, Frame 29)
    - New York (C-Z), 1976 (Reel 32, Frame 142)
    - North Carolina State University (D-W), 1976 (Reel 32, Frame 340)
    - Northern Arizona University (Bensusan, Guy), 1976 (Reel 32, Frame 370)
    - Northwestern University (Guetzkow, Harold), 1976 (Reel 32, Frame 381)
    - Ne-Nu, 1976 (Reel 32, Frame 388)
    - Oa-Ol, 1976 (Reel 32, Frame 588)
    - Op-Ov, 1976 (Reel 32, Frame 708)
    - Pa, 1976 (Reel 33, Frame 1)
    - Pe-Ph, 1976 (Reel 33, Frame 293)
    - Population Council, Inc. (M-Z), 1976 (Reel 33, Frame 556)
    - Population (F-R), 1976 (Reel 33, Frame 720)
    - Pi-Po, 1976 (Reel 33, Frame 847)
    - Psychiatric Institute Foundation (Sex Role Conference), 1976 (Reel 34, Frame 1)
    - Pr-Pu, 1976 (Reel 34, Frame 411)
    - Queens College, New York (Ethnic Materials Information Center), 1976 (Reel 34, Frame 624)
    - Ra, 1976 (Reel 34, Frame 663)
    - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (Human Dimensions), 1976 (Reel 34, Frame 740)
    - Re, 1976 (Reel 34, Frame 887)
    - Rice Center for Community Design and Research, 1976 (Reel 34, Frame 1082)
    - Rice Center for Community Design and Research (Supplementary Material), 1976 (Reel 35, Frame 1)
    - Ri, 1976 (Reel 35, Frame 154)
    - Rockefeller, 1976 (Reel 35, Frame 198)
    - Rokeach, Milton, 1976 (Reel 35, Frame 221)
    - Ro-Ru, 1976 (Reel 35, Frame 480)
    - Sa, 1976 (Reel 35, Frame 695)
    - Sc, 1976 (Reel 35, Frame 935)
    - Se, 1976 (Reel 36, Frame 1)
    - Sh, 1976 (Reel 36, Frame 14)
    - Smithsonian Institution (A-U), 1976 (Reel 36, Frame 169)
    - Si-Sm, 1976 (Reel 36, Frame 537)
    - Sn, 1976 (Reel 36, Frame 683)
    - So, 1976 (Reel 36, Frame 781)
    - Sprague, George F., 1976 (Reel 36, Frame 998)
    - Stanford University (C-W), 1976 (Reel 36, Frame 1004)
    - State University of New York at Albany (A-B), 1976 (Reel 37, Frame 1)
    - State University of New York at Binghamton (A-C), 1976 (Reel 37, Frame 178)
    - State University of New York at Brockport (Writers' Forum), 1976 (Reel 37, Frame 210)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo (C-T), 1976 (Reel 37, Frame 212)
    - State University of New York at Oswego (Summer Linguistics Institute), 1976 (Reel 37, Frame 451)
    - State University of New York at Purchase (Newberger Museum), 1976 (Reel 37, Frame 494)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook (Geiger, H. Jack), 1976 (Reel 37, Frame 500)
    - Suid, Lawrence, 1976 (Reel 37, Frame 505)
    - St-Sy, 1976 (Reel 37, Frame 840)
    - Texas (A-T), 1976 (Reel 38, Frame 1)
    - Ta-Te, 1976 (Reel 38, Frame 152)
    - Theatre Communications Group (Zeisler, Peter), 1976 (Reel 38, Frame 495)
    - Thompson, J. Walter Company, 1976 (Reel 38, Frame 580)
    - Th-To, 1976 (Reel 38, Frame 686)
    - Tr-Tw, 1976 (Reel 38, Frame 840)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (B-V), 1976 (Reel 38, Frame 1014)
    - United States, Agriculture (A-W), 1976 (Reel 39, Frame 1)
    - United States (C-N), 1976 (Reel 39, Frame 67)
    - United States (S), 1976 (Reel 39, Frame 351)
    - United States Jaycees (Threshold Program), 1976 (Reel 39, Frame 500)
    - United States National Committee for the History and Philosophy of Science, 1976 (Reel 39, Frame 531)
    - United States National Student Association (Food Action Center), 1976 (Reel 39, Frame 534)
    - United States of the World (Conference), 1976 (Reel 39, Frame 558)
    - Universite Internacional, 1976 (Reel 39, Frame 567)
    - University (A), 1976 (Reel 39, Frame 586)
    - University of California (Environmental Ethics, Santa Cruz), 1976 (Reel 39, Frame 599)
    - University of California (Santa Cruz Campus), 1976 (Reel 39, Frame 684)
    - University of California (A-W), 1976 (Reel 39, Frame 703)
    - University of Chicago (E-W), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 1)
    - University of Cincinnati (Medical Center), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 231)
    - University of Colorado (B-I), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 267)
    - University of Dallas (Morris, Robert), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 273)
    - University of Delaware (C-S), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 275)
    - University of Denver (P-S), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 403)
    - University (F-H), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 447)
    - University of Illinois (I-P), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 491)
    - University of Iowa (Drama), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 495)
    - University of Iowa, Translation Program (Supplementary Material), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 497)
    - University of Kansas (Sidman, Charles F.), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 535)
    - University (M), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 538)
    - University (N), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 713)
    - University (O-P), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 751)
    - University (R-S), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 902)
    - University (T-V), 1976 (Reel 40, Frame 1012)
    - University of Washington (E-S), 1976 (Reel 41, Frame 1)
    - University of Wisconsin (Malnutrition), 1976 (Reel 41, Frame 16)
    - University of Wisconsin, Malnutrition (Supplementary Material), 1976 (Reel 41, Frame 19)
    - University of Wisconsin (H-Y), 1976 (Reel 41, Frame 120)
    - Utah State University (B-T), 1976 (Reel 41, Frame 255)
    - Utah State University (Value Education Conference), 1976 (Reel 41, Frame 359)
    - U, 1976 (Reel 41, Frame 405)
    - Volunteer Lawyers for the Arts, 1976 (Reel 41, Frame 504)
    - V, 1976 (Reel 41, Frame 917)
    - Washington Institute for Women in Politics, 1976 (Reel 42, Frame 1)
    - Wa, 1976 (Reel 42, Frame 107)
    - We, 1976 (Reel 42, Frame 396)
    - Wh-Wi, 1976 (Reel 42, Frame 532)
    - Wofford College, 1976 (Reel 42, Frame 833)
    - Women in Public Broadcasting, 1976 (Reel 42, Frame 837)
    - Women's Action Alliance, Inc. (International Women's Project), 1976 (Reel 42, Frame 919)
    - Women's Interart Center, Inc., 1976 (Reel 43, Frame 1)
    - Wo-Wy, 1976 (Reel 43, Frame 138)
    - Yale University (H-S), 1976 (Reel 43, Frame 497)
    - X-Z, 1976 (Reel 43, Frame 650)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1976; 1976/200.A
      - C-Y, 1976 (Reel 43, Frame 777)
    - United States - Fellowships, 1976; 1976/200.E
      - Hines, Deborah H., 1976 (Reel 43, Frame 872)
    - United States - Declinations, 1976; 1976/200.F
      - B-S, 1976 (Reel 43, Frame 884)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1976; 1976/200.S
      - University of Colorado (Economics), 1976 (Reel 43, Frame 1039)
    - United States - Schistosomiasis, 1976; 1976/200.W
      - Clark Foundation, 1976 (Reel 43, Frame 1092)
  - Philippines, 1976; 1976/242
    - A-V, 1976 (Reel 44, Frame 1)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, 1976; 1976/242.E
      - Montef, Manuel S., 1976 (Reel 44, Frame 215)
  - Puerto Rico, 1976; 1976/243
    - Arbona, Guillermo, 1976 (Reel 44, Frame 218)
  - Internship Program - Minority School Superintendents, 1976; 1976/260
    - B-W, 1976 (Reel 44, Frame 220)
  - Fellowships in Higher Educational Administration (Minority), 1976; 1976/268
    - B-S, 1976 (Reel 44, Frame 267)
  - Playwrights in Residence, 1976; 1976/272
    - B-N, 1976 (Reel 44, Frame 322)
    - O-T, 1976 (Reel 44, Frame 566)
  - South America, 1976; 1976/300
    - Inter-American Development Bank, 1976 (Reel 44, Frame 659)
    - Inter-American Development Bank (Supplementary Material), 1976 (Reel 44, Frame 669)
    - Inter-American Development Bank (Molina-Vallejo, Fernando), 1976 (Reel 45, Frame 1)
    - Inter-American Development Bank, Molina-Vallejo, Fernando (Supplementary Material), 1976 (Reel 45, Frame 116)
    - F-I, 1976 (Reel 45, Frame 440)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1976; 1976/300.A
      - Pan American Federation of Medical Schools, 1976 (Reel 45, Frame 594)
    - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/300.D
      - Central American Cooperative Program for Food Improvement, 1976 (Reel 45, Frame 599)
  - Argentina, 1976; 1976/301
    - A-P, 1976 (Reel 45, Frame 601)
    - Argentina - Medical Sciences, 1976; 1976/301.A
      - Pan American Federation, 1976 (Reel 45, Frame 685)
  - Bolivia, 1976; 1976/303
    - Landivar, Juan A., 1976 (Reel 45, Frame 688)
  - Brazil, 1976; 1976/305
    - University of Bahia (A-S), 1976 (Reel 45, Frame 692)
    - A-V, 1976 (Reel 45, Frame 768)
    - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/305.D
      - Agriculture, 1976 (Reel 45, Frame 1023)
      - Rice, 1976 (Reel 45, Frame 1039)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, 1976; 1976/305.E
      - M-S, 1976 (Reel 45, Frame 1046)
  - Chile, 1976/309
    - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/309.D
      - Agricultural Research Institute, 1976 (Reel 46, Frame 1)
  - Colombia, 1976; 1976/311
    - Javeriana University (Population), 1976 (Reel 46, Frame 4)
    - Universidad del Valle (Rural Development), 1976 (Reel 46, Frame 113)
    - Universidad del Valle, Rural Development (Supplementary Material), 1976 (Reel 46, Frame 128)
    - A-U, 1976 (Reel 46, Frame 826)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/311.D
      - Colombian Agricultural Institute (Aguirre, Maria Teresa), 1976 (Reel 46, Frame 996)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, 1976; 1976/311.E
      - Jimenez Aponte, Benjamin, 1976 (Reel 46, Frame 1002)
  - Costa Rica, 1976; 1976/313
    - University of Costa Rica (Echandi Zurcher, Ronald John), 1976 (Reel 46, Frame 1006)
    - Costa Rica - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/313.D
      - Agriculture, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 1)
  - Chile, 1976; 1976/309
    - D-V, 1976 (Reel 45, Frame 1086)
  - Ecuador, 1976/317
    - Ecuador - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/317.D
      - 317D, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 4)
      - Agriculture, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 28)
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, 1976; 1976/317.E
      - Diaz Coronel, Gorky, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 33)
  - Guatemala, 1976; 1976/319
    - A-S, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 88)
  - Honduras, 1976; 1976/321
    - Silva Gomez, Antonio Ramon, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 190)
  - Mexico, 1976; 1976/323
    - A-Z, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 215)
    - Mexico - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/323.D
      - Agricultural Education (Monterrey), 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 248)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, 1976; 1976/323.E
      - Manjarrez Hernandez, Antonio, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 251)
  - Nicaragua, 1976; 1976/325
    - N-U, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 255)
  - Panama, 1976; 1976/327
    - Borlitta, Adito, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 298)
  - Paraguay, 1976; 1976/329
    - Paraguayan Development Foundation, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 300)
    - Paraguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/329.D
      - 329D, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 305)
  - Peru, 1976; 1976/331
    - E-Z, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 371)
    - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/331.D
      - University of San Marcos (Veterinary Medicine), 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 418)
  - El Salvador, 1976; 1976/333
    - Allwood P., Juan, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 447)
  - Dominican Republic, 1976; 1976/335
    - C-S, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 454)
    - Universidad Catolica Madre y Maestra (Medical School), 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 492)
  - Uruguay, 1976; 1976/337
    - Institute of Biological Sciences, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 710)
  - Venezuela, 1976; 1976/339
    - Ferriz, David, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 713)
    - Venezuela - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/339.D
      - 339D, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 716)
      - Agriculture, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 729)
  - England, 1976; 1976/401
    - B-K, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 778)
    - London School of Hygiene, 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 991)
    - University College at Buckingham (Beloff, Max), 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 1005)
    - University of Keele (Education), 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 1019)
    - University of Reading (Ellis, Peter R.), 1976 (Reel 47, Frame 1035)
    - L-Y, 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 1)
    - England - Schistosomiasis, 1976; 1976/401.W
      - British Medical Research Council (Saint Lucia Project), 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 144)
  - Ireland, 1976; 1976/403
    - University College, Dublin (Irish Folklore), 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 146)
  - Scotland, 1976; 1976/405
    - University of Edinburgh (Hale, L. J.), 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 176)
    - University of Glasgow (M), 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 182)
  - Australia, 1976; 1976/410
    - B-S, 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 187)
  - Fiji, 1976; 1976/419
    - University of the South Pacific (M-S), 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 322)
  - Caribbean Region and Central America, 1976; 1976/420
    - C, 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 354)
  - Canada, 1976; 1976/427
    - B-C, 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 470)
    - Regent College (Houston, James M.), 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 576)
    - I-U, 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 580)
  - Jamaica, 1976; 1976/437
    - Jelliffe, Derrick B., 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 851)
    - University of the West Indies (Population), 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 857)
  - Trinidad, 1976/451
    - Trinidad - Virus Studies, 1976; 1976/451.V
      - Administration, 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 884)
  - Ceylon, 1976; 1976/462
    - C-D, 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 909)
  - India, 1976; 1976/464
    - B-R, 1976 (Reel 48, Frame 942)
  - Pakistan, 1976; 1976/465
    - Pakistan Agricultural Research Center, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 1)
    - Pakistan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/465.D
      - Agriculture, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 9)
  - Bengal/Bangladesh, 1976; 1976/466
    - C-Z, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 78)
    - Bengal/Bangladesh - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/466.D
      - Agriculture, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 229)
  - New Guinea and Papua, 1976; 1976/472
    - Tobolton, Eliakim Taenge, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 270)
  - Malaysia, 1976; 1976/473
    - M-U, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 276)
  - Africa, 1976; 1976/475
    - A-P, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 326)
  - Kenya, 1976; 1976/476
    - B-O, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 364)
    - University of Nairobi (E-M), 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 410)
  - East Africa Region, 1976; 1976/477
    - East African Medical Research Council, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 461)
  - South Africa Region, 1976; 1976/487
    - N-S, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 471)
    - South Africa Region - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/487.D
      - Agriculture, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 478)
  - Cape of Good Hope, 1976; 1976/489
    - B-M, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 499)
  - Uganda, 1976; 1976/492
    - B-S, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 540)
  - Sudan, 1976; 1976/494
    - Higher Education, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 594)
    - University of Khartoum (A), 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 643)
  - West Africa, 1976; 1976/495
    - R-T, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 683)
  - Ghana, 1976; 1976/496
    - C-U, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 713)
  - Nigeria, 1976; 1976/497
    - University of Ibadan (A-T), 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 815)
    - A-Y, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 923)
    - Nigeria - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/497.D
      - University of Ibadan (Agriculture), 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 1031)
    - Nigeria - Fellowships, 1976; 1976/497.E
      - A-E, 1976 (Reel 49, Frame 1076)
    - Nigeria - Social Sciences, 1976; 1976/497.S
      - University of Ibadan (Agribusiness Management), 1976 (Reel 50, Frame 1)
  - France, 1976; 1976/500
    - A-O, 1976 (Reel 50, Frame 7)
  - Asia, 1976/600
    - Asia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/600.D
      - Rice, 1976 (Reel 50, Frame 198)
  - Taiwan, 1976; 1976/605
    - A-C, 1976 (Reel 50, Frame 275)
  - Japan, 1976; 1976/609
    - Hitotsubashi University, 1976 (Reel 50, Frame 398)
    - A-T, 1976 (Reel 50, Frame 400)
  - Korea, 1976; 1976/613
    - C-M, 1976 (Reel 50, Frame 481)
    - Yonsei University, 1976 (Reel 50, Frame 488)
  - Thailand, 1976; 1976/617
    - Kasetsart University (E-S), 1976 (Reel 50, Frame 533)
    - University of Thammasat (Puey, Ungphakorn), 1976 (Reel 50, Frame 630)
    - A-X, 1976 (Reel 50, Frame 641)
    - Pacific Trade and Development Conference (Supplementary Material), 1976 (Reel 50, Frame 912)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, 1976; 1976/617.E
      - O-Y, 1976 (Reel 51, Frame 1)
    - Thailand - Social Sciences, 1976; 1976/617.S
      - University of Thammasat (Economics), 1976 (Reel 51, Frame 12)
  - Holland, 1976; 1976/650
    - N-W, 1976 (Reel 51, Frame 92)
  - Indonesia, 1976; 1976/652
    - G-O, 1976 (Reel 51, Frame 113)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, 1976; 1976/652.E
      - A-S, 1976 (Reel 51, Frame 194)
  - Europe, 1976; 1976/700
    - Fornari, Angelina, 1976 (Reel 51, Frame 231)
  - Ethiopia, 1976; 1976/701
    - D-H, 1976 (Reel 51, Frame 289)
    - Ethiopia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/701.D
      - Agriculture, 1976 (Reel 51, Frame 309)
  - Belgium, 1976; 1976/707
    - B-C, 1976 (Reel 51, Frame 351)
  - Belgian Congo, 1976; 1976/709
    - National University of Zaire (D-S), 1976 (Reel 51, Frame 359)
    - Belgian Congo - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1976; 1976/709.D
      - Agriculture, 1976 (Reel 51, Frame 451)
    - Belgian Congo - Fellowships, 1976; 1976/709.E